{
    "subject": "resource/Ayesha_Faridi",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Ayesha Faridi is an anchor for the Indian business news channel ET Now.",
    "human_readable": "Ayesha Faridi is an anchor for the Indian business news channel ET Now.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752014875411987,
            "question": "Is Ayesha Faridi a business news anchor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7995550036430359,
            "question": "For which news channel does Ayesha Faridi work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927402257919312,
            "question": "Who is Ayesha Faridi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7633839845657349,
            "question": "Is Ayesha Faridi a well-known figure in Indian media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6944736242294312,
            "question": "What is Ayesha Faridi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47681352496147156,
            "question": "What is the name of Ayesha Faridi's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4311060905456543,
            "question": "Does Ayesha Faridi work in television?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.406221866607666,
            "question": "What type of news does ET Now cover?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3034104108810425,
            "question": "Where is ET Now based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06942261755466461,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of ET Now's programming?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ayesha Faridi is an anchor for the Indian business news channel ET Now.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5298_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is ET Now based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5298_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of news does ET Now cover?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5298_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Ayesha Faridi work in television?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5298_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5298_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention Ayesha Faridi as an anchor for the Indian business news channel, either directly (document 10) or indirectly (documents 26, 22, and 42)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Ayesha Faridi working as an anchor at various channels, including ET Now. Therefore, the statement \"Ayesha Faridi is an anchor for the Indian business news channel ET Now\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}